{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501152943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501152942"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" bfc041a2-d957-4316-a3d6-58308af8f169"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501163557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501163556"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501164130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501164130"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501164843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501164843"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501165016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501165016"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501165789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501165788"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501166824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501166823"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501169692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501169691"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TULIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501170387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501170386"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" FOLENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501171640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501171640"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501173303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501173303"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501174025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501174025"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" KUCHOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501174869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501174869"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501175743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501175743"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501176474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501176473"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501177148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501177147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501180770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501180769"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TULISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501181315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501181315"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501181465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501181464"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501181868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501181868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501182704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501182703"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501183627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501183626"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" KUPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501184326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501184325"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501184492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501184491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501185261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501185260"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501188256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501188255"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TULIFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501188735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501188734"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501189253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501189252"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501190034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501190034"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501190691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501190690"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501191335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501191334"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501191419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501191419"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501192027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501192026"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" WIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501195156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501195155"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501195298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501195298"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501196242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501196241"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501197313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501197313"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501197980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501197979"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501198432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501198432"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501199065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501199064"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501199615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501199615"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501200100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501200099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501201481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501201480"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501202133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501202133"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" KULIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501202730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501202729"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501205771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501205770"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501206156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501206156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501207152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501207151"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501207664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501207663"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501208624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501208624"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501209287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501209287"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501209910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501209910"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" YAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501212977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501212976"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501213732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501213732"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501214557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501214557"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" WALIRANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501215060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501215059"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" RANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501216002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501216001"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501216648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501216647"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501217272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501217271"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501218218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501218217"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501218677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501218677"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501219154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501219153"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501220134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501220133"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MASHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501223201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501223200"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501224506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501224505"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIPOVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501226248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501226247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501227047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501227047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501227891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501227891"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" CHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501228365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501228365"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501229593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501229592"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" KUZIANGIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501230631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501230631"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501231096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501231095"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501231726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501231726"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" UANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501235174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501235174"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501235777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501235776"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501236713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501236712"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501236906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501236906"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501237645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501237645"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501237898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501237897"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501238535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501238534"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501239936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501239935"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501240287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501240287"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501240768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501240767"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501244348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501244347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501244799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501244799"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501245456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501245455"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501246755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501246754"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501246958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501246958"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501247564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501247564"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501248801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501248800"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501249500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501249500"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501250361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501250361"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" MITUNGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501250793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501250792"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501251942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501251942"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501252672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501252671"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501255785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501255784"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501257038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501257037"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501257814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501257813"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501258446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501258445"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501259228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501259227"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501259793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501259792"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501261108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501261108"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" AKIWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501261633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501261632"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501262896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501262894"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501263736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501263736"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501263964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501263963"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501264790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501264789"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" KUJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501267611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501267611"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501268866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501268865"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501269440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501269439"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501269527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501269527"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501269960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501269959"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501270524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501270523"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501270929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501270929"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501271867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501271867"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501272738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501272735"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TULIPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501273318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501273317"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501273578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501273577"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501274346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501274345"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501277336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501277336"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501278230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501278230"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501279357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501279357"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501279842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501279841"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501280716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501280716"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" KIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501281120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501281120"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501281869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501281869"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501283187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501283187"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501284411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501284409"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TUREKEBISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501284969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501284968"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501285618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501285617"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501289088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501289088"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501290306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501290306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501291174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501291173"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" AMEPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501291788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501291788"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501292713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501292712"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501293008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501293008"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501293676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501293675"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501294717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501294716"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501295819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501295819"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" KUSAFISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501296466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501296466"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501296632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501296632"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501297048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501297047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501297765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501297764"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501300842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501300841"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501301414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501301413"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501301595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501301595"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501302372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501302371"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" MAKAMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501303189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501303188"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501304169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501304169"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501305137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501305137"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501306135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501306134"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501306892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501306892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" KUUNGANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501307084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501307084"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501307691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501307691"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501308488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501308488"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501311563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501311562"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501312410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501312409"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501313374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501313374"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501313579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501313578"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501314229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501314228"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501315417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501315416"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501316321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501316321"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" WATACHIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501316893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501316893"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501317157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501317156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501317858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501317857"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501321002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501321001"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501321886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501321885"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISEMA"," userResponse":" TULISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501322129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501322128"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501322796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501322794"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501323289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501323289"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501324665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501324664"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501325800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501325799"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUBADILISHE"," userResponse":" TUBADILISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501326530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501326529"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501327233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501327232"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501329639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501329638"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501330110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501330110"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501330757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501330757"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501331832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501331831"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501332314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501332313"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501333300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501333299"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501334697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501334696"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATATUA"," userResponse":" TUKATATUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501335192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501335191"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501335555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501335555"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501338455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501338454"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501338587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501338586"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501347325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501347325"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501354360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501354360"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c968bb1c-a714-4f15-a62d-e5d39fd87a20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501364052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501364052"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501364433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501364432"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501364928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501364928"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501365284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501365283"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501365697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501365697"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501366181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501366181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501366414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501366413"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501369653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501369653"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501369698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501369698"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501370425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501370424"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501370828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501370828"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501371128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501371128"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501371335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501371335"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501371538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501371538"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501371861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501371861"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501372093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501372093"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501375305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501375304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501375719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501375718"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501378327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501378327"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501378538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501378537"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501378745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501378745"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501381047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501381046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501381122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501381121"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501387190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501387189"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501514912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501514911"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" d9ac831e-3664-4b17-ad94-8780e24d7065"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501515005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501515005"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 76e747fd-6e0f-47ff-b3cc-5d5b5414d8d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501524957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501524956"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 6b5dc123-5739-45bb-9678-ce57d51c03e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501525342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501525341"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 6b5dc123-5739-45bb-9678-ce57d51c03e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501525835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501525835"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 6b5dc123-5739-45bb-9678-ce57d51c03e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501526182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501526181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 6b5dc123-5739-45bb-9678-ce57d51c03e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501526264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501526264"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 6b5dc123-5739-45bb-9678-ce57d51c03e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501526339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501526339"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 6b5dc123-5739-45bb-9678-ce57d51c03e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501537939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501537938"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 6b5dc123-5739-45bb-9678-ce57d51c03e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501547578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501547578"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 6b5dc123-5739-45bb-9678-ce57d51c03e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501588478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501588478"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" cbffe915-7777-482c-aae6-f8e3ed7c9f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitafanyaje?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAFANYAJE"," userResponse":" NITAFANYAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501754562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501754560"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" cbffe915-7777-482c-aae6-f8e3ed7c9f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je nitafanyaje?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501754655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501754655"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 9138161c-fe6b-40c9-87d0-8ce99a426238"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo usishangae unapoliona pua la nguruwe jinsi lilivyo kwa sababu limekuwa hivyo tangu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501765155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501765155"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 9138161c-fe6b-40c9-87d0-8ce99a426238"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo usishangae unapoliona pua la nguruwe jinsi lilivyo kwa sababu limekuwa hivyo tangu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501773430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501773429"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 9138161c-fe6b-40c9-87d0-8ce99a426238"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo usishangae unapoliona pua la nguruwe jinsi lilivyo kwa sababu limekuwa hivyo tangu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501783575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501783575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c7e1996d-933c-4c3a-8bdc-0bfcc9cb7f7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501783955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501783954"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c7e1996d-933c-4c3a-8bdc-0bfcc9cb7f7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501784437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501784437"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c7e1996d-933c-4c3a-8bdc-0bfcc9cb7f7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501784478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501784478"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c7e1996d-933c-4c3a-8bdc-0bfcc9cb7f7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501784557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501784556"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c7e1996d-933c-4c3a-8bdc-0bfcc9cb7f7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501827126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501827125"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" c7e1996d-933c-4c3a-8bdc-0bfcc9cb7f7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501827182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501827182"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 4efc5e90-3729-489c-b40a-dfbcaae10571"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIFIKA"," userResponse":" ULIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501835641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501835641"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 4efc5e90-3729-489c-b40a-dfbcaae10571"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501841059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501841058"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 4efc5e90-3729-489c-b40a-dfbcaae10571"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501846888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501846887"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 4efc5e90-3729-489c-b40a-dfbcaae10571"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501857770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501857770"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501857993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501857993"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501858957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501858957"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501860245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501860244"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501863150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501863149"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501864006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501864006"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501864330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501864330"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501865569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501865569"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501869157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501869156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501870152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501870151"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501870409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501870409"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501871381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501871381"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501874292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501874292"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501875337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501875337"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501875817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501875817"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501880397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501880397"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501880491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501880491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501884852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501884852"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501889779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501889778"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501894593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501894592"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501904147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501904146"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501910099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501910099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501916351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501916351"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501923382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501923382"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501929234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501929234"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501934422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501934422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501939229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501939229"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501944543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501944542"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501954706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501954705"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501962920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501962920"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501969015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501969015"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501978510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501978510"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501984189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501984189"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 85129af0-65c7-4854-9e17-6063c818d3fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_13"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501993433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501993433"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 12000b04-f70c-464c-8bd8-c3037ae00313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501994490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501994490"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 12000b04-f70c-464c-8bd8-c3037ae00313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501998145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501998144"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 12000b04-f70c-464c-8bd8-c3037ae00313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548501999199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548501999198"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 12000b04-f70c-464c-8bd8-c3037ae00313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548502001962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548502001962"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 12000b04-f70c-464c-8bd8-c3037ae00313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548502003016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548502003016"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 12000b04-f70c-464c-8bd8-c3037ae00313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548502003649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548502003649"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 12000b04-f70c-464c-8bd8-c3037ae00313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548502003760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548502003760"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 12000b04-f70c-464c-8bd8-c3037ae00313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548502009527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548502009527"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_141222"," gameId":" 12000b04-f70c-464c-8bd8-c3037ae00313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}